(Howard:)Completely empty box,
if you'd like to examine it.
(Leonard:)Mm-hm.
(Leonard:)Yep. I see nothing in this box
but a wasted childhood.
(Howard:)Little snarky there, cello lessons.
(Howard:)We have this completely ordinary
cylinder if you'd like to examine it.
(Raj:)Ordinary, yet I sense it
is dripping with magical potential.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord.
(Sheldon:)A man pops out for a moment
to evacuate his bowels...
(Sheldon:)...and catch up on the adventures
of the Caped Crusader only to emerge...
(Sheldon:)...and discover his apartment has been
transformed into a cabaret.
Sheldon, he's practicing
for his cousin's birthday party.
(Howard:)As I was saying,
empty box, empty cylinder, and...
(Sheldon:)Ooh!
Voilá.
I'm telling you, there's a seat on the
Hogwart's Express with your name on it.
(Sheldon:)This is how you're going to entertain
your little cousin and his friends?